(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
(شاهد على www.dramacool.club دعم الإدارة)
Zhu Wenjie.
تشو ون جيه.
Mr. Lin,
السيد لين،
it seems someone's coming.
يبدو أن أحدهم قادم.
don't make too much noise.
لا تُصدر ضجيجاً كبيراً.
Yes.
نعم.
It's me.
هذا أنا.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
You...
أنت...
Don't you recognize me?
ألا تعرفني؟
Time is tight. Listen to me.
الوقت ضيق. استمع إليّ.
Stay away from the Lin family.
ابتعد عن عائلة لين.
The Lin family is too complicated
عائلة لين معقدة للغاية
for you to understand.
لكي تفهم.
Over there.
هناك.
Vivi, hide well.
فيفي، اختبئي جيداً.
I can't lose you again.
لا أستطيع أن أفقدك مرة أخرى.
Over here. Hurry and chase.
هنا. أسرعوا والحقوا بهم.
I hope
آمل
someone will expose Lin Moxiao's true colors
سيكشف أحدهم حقيقة لين موكسياو
[through this marriage certificate.]
[من خلال شهادة الزواج هذه.]
[Who is he?]
[من هو؟]
What are you looking at?
ما الذي تنظر إليه؟
He's the one on the marriage certificate.
هو الشخص المذكور في عقد الزواج.
Who is the woman in his arms just now?
من هي المرأة التي بين ذراعيه الآن؟
Find out.
اكتشف ذلك.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
Mr. Lin,
السيد لين،
should we reveal this news
هل ينبغي لنا الكشف عن هذا الخبر؟
to Zhu Wenjie?
إلى تشو ون جيه؟
After all,
في النهاية،
she has always liked Lin Moqing unilaterally.
لطالما كانت معجبة بلين موكينغ من طرف واحد.
Whether I'm unrequited or not,
سواء كان حبي من طرف واحد أم لا،
it's not for you to decide.
ليس من شأنك أن تقرر.
Don't forget,
لا تنسى،
the Lin Group is the one
مجموعة لين هي واحدة
seeking help from the Zhu family.
طلب المساعدة من عائلة تشو.
You should know
يجب أن تعلم
what should be said
ما الذي ينبغي قوله
and what shouldn't.
وما لا ينبغي أن يكون.
After all these years,
بعد كل هذه السنوات،
your temper hasn't changed a bit.
لم يتغير مزاجك قيد أنملة.
Take care of your people.
اهتم بشعبك.
Sorry,
آسف،
[The number you've dialed is busy.]
[الرقم الذي طلبته مشغول.]
[Please...]
[لو سمحت...]
[Sorry,]
[آسف،]
[the number you've dialed is powered off.]
[الرقم الذي طلبته مطفأ.]
Why isn't anyone picking up?
لماذا لا يرد أحد على الهاتف؟
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
Did you go to see Lan Hewei?
هل ذهبت لرؤية لان هيوي؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I shouldn't have asked you to come.
ما كان ينبغي لي أن أطلب منك المجيء.
It's all my fault.
كل هذا خطأي.
Happy birthday to you.
عيد ميلاد سعيد.
Vivi,
أنت تعيش،
I'll always be with you on your birthday.
سأكون معك دائماً في عيد ميلادك.
I have
أملك
a bracelet just like yours.
سوار مثل سوارك تماماً.
Thank you, Mengmeng. It's beautiful.
شكراً لكِ يا منغمينغ. إنه جميل.
Don't take it off.
لا تخلعه.
Mengmeng. Three.
منغمنغ. ثلاثة.
Lin Mojiao is going to kill me.
لين موجياو ستقتلني.
I'm on my way.
أنا في طريقي.
Find a safe place to hide. [Two.]
ابحث عن مكان آمن للاختباء. [اثنان.]
Vivi.
أنت حي.
Don't hang up.
لا تغلق الخط.
I'll be there soon.
سأكون هناك قريباً.
[One.]
[واحد.]
I remember now.
أتذكر الآن.
Lin Mojiao wants to kill me.
لين موجياو تريد قتلي.
Who is he?
من هو؟
Why is he impersonating Lin Mojiao?
لماذا ينتحل شخصية لين موجياو؟
Vivi.
أنت حي.
You're awake.
فيفي، لقد استيقظتِ.
Weiwei,
ويوي,
what are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Why are you pretending to be my husband?
لماذا تتظاهر بأنك زوجي؟
It seems you've remembered everything.
يبدو أنك تذكرت كل شيء.
Qingyou,
تشينغيو,
I didn't expect
لم أتوقع
the Lin family's illegitimate child
الطفل غير الشرعي لعائلة لين
to be alive.
أن يكون المرء على قيد الحياة.
I'm not an illegitimate child.
أنا لست طفلاً غير شرعي.
You saved me from the hospital, didn't you?
لقد أنقذتني من المستشفى، أليس كذلك؟
What are your intentions?
ما هي نواياك؟
Because I like you.
لأنني معجب بك.
I don't want you to go back to my brother.
لا أريدك أن تعود إلى أخي.
It seems you don't want to talk.
يبدو أنك لا تريد التحدث.
Why did you save me?
لماذا أنقذتني؟
Don't you want to know my purpose?
ألا تريد أن تعرف غايتي؟
Actually, we are the same.
في الحقيقة، نحن متشابهون.
What purpose could I have?
ما الغاية التي قد أسعى إليها؟
I want to take back Lin Group.
أريد استعادة مجموعة لين.
You want to take back Blue Crane.
تريد استعادة بلو كرين.
These two companies
هاتان الشركتان
are in the hands of one person.
هي في يد شخص واحد.
So this is why you
لهذا السبب أنت
pretend to be Lin Mojiao?
هل تتظاهر بأنك لين موجياو؟
I just want you
أريدك أنت فقط
to get used to the identity of Mrs Lin in advance.
للتعود على هوية السيدة لين مسبقاً.
And
و
to cultivate
لزراعة
feelings with your future ally.
مشاعرك تجاه حليفك المستقبلي.
We are a good match,
نحن متوافقان تماماً،
aren't we?
أليس كذلك؟
This is a win-win deal.
هذه صفقة رابحة للجميع.
Win-win?
مكسب للجميع؟
I can take back Blue Crane
أستطيع استعادة بلو كرين
I can get Blue Crane back myself.
أستطيع استعادة بلو كرين بنفسي.
Does it look familiar?
هل يبدو مألوفاً؟
How could Meng be with you?
كيف يمكن أن يكون مينغ معك؟
So,
لذا،
shall we cooperate?
هل نتعاون؟
It seems Lin Mojiao
يبدو أن لين موجياو
can't hold back anymore.
لم يعد بإمكاني التراجع.
You're so skilled now.
لقد أصبحت ماهراً جداً الآن.
If Lin Mojiao finds out,
إذا علمت لين موجياو بذلك،
what do you want to do?
ماذا تريد أن تفعل؟
I'll take care of these people for you.
سأعتني بهؤلاء الأشخاص نيابةً عنك.
I'll also take good care
سأعتني بنفسي جيداً
your bestie.
صديقتك المقربة.
Nice to meet you again,
سررت بلقائك مجدداً.
Ms. Zhu.
السيدة تشو.
I'm Lin Moqing.
أنا لين موكينغ.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Zhu.
تشرفت بلقائك يا سيد تشو.
Thank you all.
شكراً لكم جميعاً.
Can she do it?
هل تستطيع فعل ذلك؟
She's the only heir of Blue Crane,
هي الوريثة الوحيدة لـ"بلو كرين"،
and the legal wife of Lin Mojiao.
والزوجة الشرعية لـ لين موجياو.
As long as she shows up
طالما أنها تحضر
at the engagement party,
في حفل الخطوبة،
[his marriage with Zhu Group,]
[زواجه من مجموعة تشو]
[and his plan to take over Blue Crane]
[وخطة للاستيلاء على بلو كرين]
[will all be ruined.]
[سوف يفسد كل شيء.]
Mojiao. Uncle.
موجياو. عمي.
Aunt.
عمة.
The banquet was prepared in a hurry.
تم إعداد الوليمة على عجل.
If there's anything we missed,
إذا كان هناك أي شيء فاتنا،
I hope you two
أتمنى لكما كل التوفيق
will forgive us.
سوف يسامحنا.
Satisfied.
راضي.
Jie,
هم،
Mr. Lin means well.
السيد لين يقصد الخير.
Don't be so rude.
لا تكن وقحاً إلى هذا الحد.
That's not the way to be.
هذه ليست الطريقة الصحيحة.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
Uncle, Aunt,
عمي، عمتي،
our families have always been close.
لطالما كانت عائلاتنا مترابطة.
And you have been very kind to me.
وقد كنت لطيفاً جداً معي.
Actually, at this party,
في الواقع، في هذه الحفلة،
I have something important
لدي شيء مهم
to ask you to be a witness for me.
أطلب منك أن تكون شاهداً لي.
Everyone,
الجميع،
first,
أولاً،
thank you for coming to my humble home
شكراً لقدومكم إلى منزلي المتواضع
to attend the celebration banquet
لحضور مأدبة الاحتفال
of Lin Group and Zhu Rong.
من مجموعة لين وتشو رونغ.
Next,
التالي،
I want to take this opportunity
أريد أن أغتنم هذه الفرصة
to announce something to everyone.
لإعلان شيء ما للجميع.
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
two years ago,
قبل عامين،
I had already married Miss Lan Hewei
لقد تزوجت بالفعل من الآنسة لان هيوي
from the Blue Crane Group.
من مجموعة بلو كرين.